Previously on desperate housewives
前情提要
We're getting married.
我们要结婚了
One proposal led to another.
求婚双双而至
We're with immigration.
我们是移民局的
- But the law get in the way.
-法律拦路
Can't this wait?
能等等吗
we're about get marry
我们就要结婚了
- Not today, you're not.
-今天可不行
A break-in was staged...
一场入室抢劫上演...
Orson, we've been robbed.
奥森  我们被盗了
In an attempt to hide assets in a divorce.
力保在离婚风暴中全身而退
- After the crash...
-车祸发生后...
And the truth
事实真相
about the accident came out
浮出水面
Mike told 'em that he was driving, but it wasn't true.
麦克告诉别人是他开的车  其实是我
The thing you have to understand
有关大卫·威廉姆斯你必须得知道
About dave williams is he wanted to be forgiven.
他祈望得到原谅
That's why he made the videotape.
这是他留下这段录像的原因
I didn't want to kill M.J. Delfino.
我不想杀掉M.J·德尔非诺
I had to.
我必须这么做
Susan Mayer killed my wife and daughter.
苏珊·梅尔害死了我的妻子和女儿
The police called it... an accident.
警方称这是一起...事故
But i don't believe a person
但我不认同一个夺取
Who takes two precious lives
两条生命的人
Should be allowed to just...
怎么能可以
Walk away.
偷生在世
I know some people will wonder,
我知道有的人可能会想
Why didn't i just kill susan?
为什么不杀掉苏珊
But what good would that have done?
但如果那样做
She'd be dead. There'd be no...
她会死掉  那样永远不会知道
Suffering.
煎熬的滋味
And to those who hate me
因为我夺去无辜男孩生命
Because i took the life...
而憎恨我的人们
Of an innocent young boy, i say...
我想说...
Aw, crap.
该死
Yes, Dave Williams wanted everyone to forgive him...
是的  大卫·威廉姆斯期望得到人们的原谅
Look, i got a new tackle box for our trip on saturday.
看  我可以在星期六的郊游中用我的新钓鱼盒了
But not until he finished doing...
在他结束这一切
The unforgivable.
不能原谅的罪恶之后
更多字幕请访问 http://www.yyets.net/
本字幕由人人影视  荣誉出品
校对：小门柴
翻译：桃金娘银  小天天鱼  Joanna  Sadnessleaf  小门柴
总监：小门柴
时间轴：娅娅  Sadnessleaf  小门柴
After the white horse nightclub
在一场蹊跷的大火
Was destroyed by a suspicious fire,
吞噬了白马俱乐部后
One body was left unclaimed.
留下了一具无人认领的尸首
The detectives on this case referred to him as...
调查此案的侦探把此称之为
"john doe a-37."
"无名氏 a-37"
For months, they tried to identify him.
他们辗转数月  想确认他的身份
Then one day, they got a call from an impound lot.
一天  他们接到从扣押处打来的电话
It seems a car had been towed from the club parking lot
对方称在俱乐部纵火那晚
The night of the fire--
一辆停在俱乐部的车被拖
A sedan that had been rented...
而租这辆车的人
To a dr. samuel heller from boston,
是波士顿的塞缪尔·海勒医生
Who had been reported missing four months earlier.
他已经在4个月前被报失踪
The doctor's dental records confirmed their theory.
受害人的牙齿记录证实了他们的猜测
His receptionist, however,
尽管如此  他的接待小姐
Did not.
却不相信
No way.
不可能
Dr. Heller did not die in that fire.
海勒医生没有死
Ma'am, we've got his dental records.
夫人  我们已经得到了牙齿记录
I don't care. You said the fire was four months go?
那又怎样  你说大火发生在4个月前
Well, i've gotten texts from him since then.
在那之后我还收到他传的短讯
You have?
你收到过
Yeah. the last one was just a few weeks ago.
上一条还是在几周前
Maybe we should send a text back.
也许我们应该回发一条
Ma'am, you have your phone with you?
夫人  你带手机了吗?
Hey, dave.
大卫
I was gonna call you.
我正准备打给你
- You were?
-是吗
Yeah. um. did you say something to M.J.
你有和M.J.聊过
- About going on that fishing trip?
-去钓鱼的事情吗
Yeah, i did.
对  我们有聊过
I know how depress you were since Jackson was deported
我知道杰克逊被遣返后你很难过
So i thought, now is the perfect time
我认为这是最佳时机
For the three of us to go up to the lake. and...
我们三个一块去湖边  而且...
I got m.j. his own little life vest.
我还给他买了儿童用的救生衣
I wish i could, but i can't.
我很乐意去  但是我不能
- I'm worried about Jackson.
-我很担心杰克逊
All the more reasons
借口总有许多
You know what they say about fishing--
你知道人们是怎么评价钓鱼的吗
It's nature's tranquilizer.
宁静怡然
Dave, i haven't heard Jackson since he was taken away
大卫  杰克逊走后我连他的一点消息都没有
And i just wanna be here in case he calls.
我想留下来  说不定他会打电话过来
Yeah, well, that's okay. just bring your cell phone.
好啊  你可以带上手机啊
I'd just feel more comfortable if i'm close by.
但待在家里  我感觉心定些
Oh, that's crazy.
疯狂的想法
I mean, Jackson wouldn't want you sittin' around here
我想杰克逊可不想你
Worrying about him.
天天坐在家里为他担心
I'm sorry. We'll go fishing another time.
我很抱歉  下次再约吧
Don't you think you're being a little selfish here?
你不觉得你这么做很自私吗
I mean, what about M.J.?
想想M.J.
You wanna go fishing, don't you, buddy? yeah!
你很想去钓鱼  是吧  伙计
Yeah.
对
What are you doing?
你在做什么
I just told you i can't go.
我说过了我去不了
I'm just thinking about m.j.
不过M.J.
He'll be fine.
他很好
You know what? you're right.
或许你是对的
I'm sorry.
对不起
It's just a trip.
不过是次郊游
You're not listening!
你根本就没有在听
Six months in europe would be educational.
去欧洲待6个月很有教育意义的
You know what would be more educational?
你知道怎么会更有教育意义吗
You going to college like we talked about.
你去上大学
Mom, i've already been in school for 12 years already.
妈妈  我在学校呆了12年了
- I... i need a vacation.
-我想要休假
Well, it seems like,
如果
based on your last visa records
看看你上次的签证记录似乎
You've already been on vacation.
你已经旅行过一次了
I'm gonna be 18. if i wanna go to europe, i'll go to europe.
我就要18岁了  如果我想去  我会去
Oh? well, good luck paying for it,
哦  是吗  那祈祷你有钱支付吧
Because if you so much as apply for a passport,
如果你这么想要申请护照
- We're cuttin' you off.
-我们会停掉你零花钱
Cut off from the
从势力强大的斯加沃
mighty scavo family fortune. Oh,no
家庭财产里扣吗  我好怕
Tom, why didn't you help me out there?
汤姆  你都不帮帮我
Because i agree with him.
因为我站在他那一边
What?
什么
Well, he's young. he should be having fun.
他年轻气盛  正是享受生命的好时光
I mean, look--look at me. i'm a middle-aged man
我是说  你看看我  一个中年男人
Reading the want ads for jobs that i'll never get.
看着我永远不可能得到工作的招聘信息
I should've gone to europe when
我有机会的话
i had the chance
我也不会错过去欧洲的
Our son is throwing his life away.
我们的儿子在虚耗光阴
We have got to keep him on track.
我们得让他按部就班地生活
What is so great about the track?
按部就班有什么好
I was on it. i did everything i was supposed to.
我就是  我做了我应该做的一切
It chewed me up and spit me out.
结果呢  它把我嚼碎又吐出来了
I know you're discouraged,
我知道你很沮丧
But... letting our son make a huge mistake
但纵容我们的儿子犯大错
- Is not gonna help anything.
-是不能帮助他成长的
Even if it is a huge mistake,
即使是个大错误
You got to let people make some
你也应该让他们
decisions about their own life
去做出生命中的一些决定
Your way is not the only way.
你的教育方式并不是权威的
I am just trying to help preston
我只是想帮普雷斯顿
Avoid the way marked "unemployable loser."
不让他去走失业又失败的人生
Fine. what do you want me to do?
好的  你想我做什么
I want you to get this stupid europe idea out of his head.
我想你让他打消去欧洲的蠢主意
Take him on a tour of the campus.
带他去参观一下大学
Get him excited. show him college could be fun.
让他对大学感兴趣  让他看看大学里的乐子
Sure.
没问题
And on the way home, i'll show my college diploma
回来的路上我要给汉堡屋的人
To the guy at the burger barn.
看我的大学文凭
Yeah. they're hiring a new fry cook for the night shift.
他们在雇一个值夜班的煎炸师傅
If you're really stopping by there,
如果你真的去那里
Bring home some onion rings.
带一些洋葱圈回来
Mommy, what are you doing?
妈妈  你在做什么
We're going to a family reunion
我们要去康妮姨妈家
at aunt connie'
参加家庭聚会
And i want to look my best.
我想成为最漂亮的
Is it gonna be fun?
很好玩吗
Well, if your idea of a good time
如果你认为好玩就是
Is sitting on rusty lawn chairs in the driveway
坐在车道生锈的草坪椅上
Eating lard in the shape of chicken,
吃一坨鸡形的猪油
- Then yeah! it's gonna be a blast.
-那你会觉得有趣极了
The driveway?
车道上
Honey, you're 6 now,
亲爱的  你6岁了
So i think it's time we had a little mother/daughter talk.
我觉得是时候和你进行母女对话了
Your father's side of the family's trash.
你父亲那一边的亲戚糟透了
Any questions?
有问题吗
If you don't like her,
如果你不喜欢她
Why are you putting on your best jewelry?
为什么还戴你最美的珠宝
'cause thas what grownups do, sweetie.
亲爱的  大人都这么做
When we don't like someone, we don't punch them
讨厌别人  并不需要拳脚相加
Or say mean things. we just find subtle ways
或恶言以对  我们能狡猾地想一些办法
To make them feel bad about their lives.
让他们自觉人生无趣
Ooh, like these earrings. aunt connie can't afford them,
像这些耳环  康妮姨妈是买不起的
And that'll make her sad.
会让她感到难过
And this will bring her to her knees.
这个会打得她单膝跪下
And this will be a kick in her throat.
而这个  则能还击她的喉舌
If you hate 'em so much, maybe we shouldn't go.
如果你那么讨厌她  你干脆就别去
Oh, no, sweetie. we have to go. they're family.
不  亲爱的  我们必须去  她们是亲戚
See, this is why i wanted to check on my things.
看吧  这就是为什么我需要检查一下
You don't leave a valuable painting on the damn floor.
一幅价值不菲的画怎么能放在这种地方
You need to put something underneath it.
你需要在下面垫一些东西
Fine. how about this ugly doormat?
好的  这个门垫呢
That is not a doormat.
这不是门垫
That is a handwoven kurdish kazak rug.
这是库尔德哈萨克人手工编织的小地毯
You know, bree, when i hang out with you,
布里  你知道吗  和你在一起的时候
I realize how little i know
我才知道自己知识多狭窄
And how much i don't give a crap.
我的废话也少了
Give me that.
把它给我
I'm so glad this divorce is almost over.
我很高兴你们就快离婚了
An obnoxious, unpleasant man will be out of my life,
一个可憎的  讨厌的男人就要离开我的生活了
And so will orson.
当然还有奥森
Hey, it's not over yet.
这并没有结束
You still got a couple of hurdles.
你还有几个障碍
Has orson brought up the insurance claim again?
奥森又提出保险索赔了吗
No, he thinks i filed it.
没有 他以为申请了
Great. when he realizes you never did, you'll be divorced,
太棒了  当他意识到你没申请时  你们早已两散
He'll be broke, and it won't matter.
他会破产  到那时也没有关系了
Yes, and i'll be single again,
我会再次孤单
And i can concentrate on my business,
我可以全心工作
Maybe do some traveling.
或许去旅行一下
Maybe spend a little time
也许花点时间
At the intersection of right leg and left leg,
找个情人
-If you know what i'm saying.
-如果你知道我在说什么
sadly,
真遗憾
karl, i always know what you are saying.
卡尔  我知道
You know, you want, i could set you up.
如果你愿意  我可以帮你
I know a lot of great guys who are good for a free dinner.
我认识很多男同胞  很优秀
And a few laughs, huh?
也能逗你开心
Thanks, karl. I'm not even divorced yet,
谢谢  卡尔  我还没离婚呢
And once I am, I don't think you'd be my first choice
就算我离婚了  也不会找你来
- As a matchmaker.
-帮我介绍对象
oh, shoot.
糟糕啦
Hello?
喂
Hey, susan, it's me.
苏珊  是我
Jackson, i have been so worried.
杰克逊  我很担心你
- Where--where are you?
-你在哪
fairview jail.
美景镇监狱
They're processing my deportation papers.
他们正在做我的驱逐文件
So they're sending you back? when?
他们要把你赶回去  什么时候
Couple days.
就这几天了
I just wanted to call and say thank you and...
我只是想打电话感谢你
Tell you that i'll miss you.
我会想你的
Well... i'll miss you, too.
我也会想你的
I mean, you came in my life
当我在人生低谷时
When i was going through a really hard time,
你走进了我的生活
And you were amazing.
你真是个好人
I mean, you are amazing.
给我留下美好回忆
You, too.
你也是
Did the immigration people tell you
那移民局的人有没有跟你说
- How they found out about you?
-他们怎么找到你的
anonymous tip.
匿名举报
Although it's pretty obvious wh"anonymous" is.
尽管这个匿名非常地显而易见
Does mike really think i'm that stupid?
麦克真的认为我是傻子吗
Mike? you think mike did this?
麦克  你觉得是麦克干的吗
Who else?
还能有谁
Mike and katherine were the only people who knew.
只有麦克和凯瑟琳知道
Katherine was doing cartwheels
凯瑟琳还帮咱们
about us getting married
"结婚"
Yeah, but, no, this doesn't make any sense
是啊  但  不  这说不通啊
Because mike knew that it wasn't for real.
因为麦克知道这不是真的
Well, real or not, he had the look of a guy
不管真的假的  他明显
Who's not ready to give you up, so--
对你还有感觉
Time's up.
时间到了
Uh, I-I gotta go.
我要挂了
I'll try and call you again before I leave.
走之前我会再给你打电话的
Hey!
回来了
Hey, hey, how was the campus tour?
你们回来了  校园参观进行得如何
Fantastic. oh!
很棒
Oh, my god. That school is amazing.
天哪  学校很棒
Oh. the professors are so engaged,
教授们都忙忙碌碌的
And the kids were open and friendly.
学生们思想开放  态度亲和
Really?
真的吗
Yeah. It was inspiring. you were so right to send us.
非常令人振奋  让我们去是正确的
Good. good. I knew if you saw the campus,
真好  我知道如果你参观过校园
You'd have a change of heart.
你就会改变心意了
Me? nah. I'm still ing to europe.
我吗  错了  我还是要去欧洲
What was that? I thought you said the tour was fantastic.
什么  你说学院参观很棒啊
Okay, so preston still needs a little convincing.
所以还需要再劝劝普雷斯顿
But I don't.
但我心意已定了
I'm going back to school.
我要去上学
Wh-what's that now?
现在是什么情况
Okay. I know it's a little out of left field,
我知道  这听起来有点离谱
But walking across the quad, i felt so alive.
但当我走在校园里  我觉得我又重生了
I spoke with someone in admissions,
我和招生处的老师谈了
And all i have to do is pass an entrance exam.
我只要通过入学考试就行了
So...
所以
you would be a college student... again.
你要去上大学  再上一次
25 years after the first time.
25年后  又一次
But this time--focused.
但是  这次  非常专注
This time, knowing exactly what i wanna major in.
这次  我非常清楚我要学什么
Which is?
是什么
Chinese.
汉语
Chinese?
As in "moo goo gai pan" chinese?
是"蘑菇鸡片"的那种中文
What's he gonna do with that,
他学这个干什么
Watch Bruce Lee movies without the subtitles?
为了看李小龙电影  不用看字幕吗
We didn't get that far.
我们还没谈到这个呢
I felt faint, and he left to go buy a backpack.
然后我头都昏了  他跑出买书包了
Ooh. lynette, that's bad.
勒奈特  这可不好
Well, it's just so random, and the worst part is
太天马行空了  更糟的是
If i point that out, i'm a bitch.
如果我说这个不好  我又成坏人了
Why is that?
为什么会这样
When did being practical and realistic
什么时候说真话和实事求是
Become synonymous with bitchiness?
变成坏人的同义词
The first time a man did something stupid,
当一个男人干了些蠢事
And a woman pointed it out.
女人把它说出来的时候
I know tom. he's going to learn
我知道汤姆  他去学中文
how to count to ten in Chinese
也只是从一数到十  学个皮毛
Then he'll get bored and move on to his new dream
然后他就会感到无聊  再找到他的新目标
Of becoming a beekeeper. well, then you
比如想当个养蜂人之类
have no choice. bite the bullet and be bitch.
那你没什么选择  当回坏人吧
No, she has a choice.
不  她可以选择
It's entirely possible to get what you want
你完全能得到你想要
Without being perceived of as a nagging shrew.
而且不用当个唠唠叨叨的泼妇
Please, sensei, instruct me in your ancient ways.
师傅(日语)  求你了  给我点秘笈吧
Well, the key is to not let them know what you're doing.
关键就是你不能让他们知道  你在做什么
This requires observation, cunning and manipulation.
这需要观察力  操纵力以及狡黠的头脑
Isn't it just easier to shut down your hoo-ha
跟他大吵一架  让他屈服
- Until he gives in?
-不是更容易一些吗
I think that bree is right--
我觉得布里是对的
That the more tom sees you digging in your heels,
你越坚持极力反对
The more he's gonna wanna do it.
汤姆就会越想做他想要的
So you wait for an opportunity
所以你只要等待一个机会
That you can use to your advantage
可以让你大展拳脚
While at the same time appearing supportive.
但同时你要表现的非常支持他
That's your advice
这就是你的建议
Hope an opportunity just drops in my lap?
等着天上掉馅饼吗
Might as well start shopping for beekeeper suits.
我还不如开始买养蜂人的制服
Oh, you guys, I'm sorry. I gotta run.
抱歉  我出去一趟
Hey. I need to talk to Mike.
我要跟麦克谈谈
Oh, he's in the shower, but I'll tell him
他在洗澡呢  我会跟他说
- you stopped by.
-你来过了
oh, no need, I will wait.
不用  我等他
Orson, I'm home.
奥森  我回来了
Have a seat.
坐下
So there never was a robbery.
根本就没有盗窃
You took these things, hoping to hide them from me.
你拿走那些东西  想藏起来
And though I've tried to come up with a reason, I can't.
我知道为什么  但苦死不得其解
So I'm forced to ask the question why.
我不得不问你原因
Why would you do such a thing?
你为什么要这么做
I want a divorce.
我想离婚
I'm sorry. I don't understand.
抱歉  我不明白
My lawyer says you're entitled to half of everything
我的律师跟我说  你会分走你我结婚期间
We've acquired during the marriage,
共同所得的财产的一半
So I was trying to hide some of those things,
我想藏起一部分
Since--let's face it-- i paid for them.
直说吧  这事儿是我花钱操办的
You've already hired a lawyer?
你已经雇了个律师吗
Yes, but I'm tired of all the lying
是  我已经不想再说谎了
And the sneaking around, so I will inform him
不想再偷偷摸摸了  所以我会通知他
- you can have whatever you like.
-你要什么  悉随尊便
I don't want a divorce.
可我不想离
Well, that part's non-negotiable.
这个不由你商量
Can't we at least talk about this?
我们不能再谈谈吗
There's no point.
没什么好谈的
So you should get a piece of paper, start to make a list
你拿张纸  列个清单吧
Of what it is you wish to take with you.
写上你想拿走什么
So... you don't want any of it?
你什么都不要了吗
No. all i want is out.
不  我只想离婚
You know, he might be a while. sure i can't help you?
他可能还要洗一会呢  不能跟我说吗
No, i need to talk to mike.
不  我要跟麦克说
Now you could flush the toilet
不如你去刷厕所
and try to get him out there
把他赶出来
You seem upset.
你好象心情不好
Something happened?
出什么事了
Did mike turn jackson in to immigration?
是不是麦克跟移民局告密  揭发杰克逊的
No. why would he do that?
不  他怎么会这么做
I don't know. jealousy?
我不知道  嫉妒吗
Jackson thinks mike is still hung up on me.
杰克逊觉得  麦克对我还余情未了
Trust me, susan. mike did not turn jackson in.
相信我  苏珊  麦克没有举报杰克逊
Mm. shower's off.
别洗了
I guess we'll know in a few seconds.
马上就能知道真相了
Listen... mike couldn't have called immigration
听我说  麦克不可能给移民局打电话
Because i never told him
因为我没告诉他
That jackson was marrying you for a green card.
杰克逊跟你结婚是为了拿绿卡
Well, somebody did, because he sent me a text
那是有人干的  因为他还给我发短信
Agreeing to keep paying me alimony.
同意帮我付赡养费
That was me.
那是我发的
I sent it.
我发的短信
Are you insane? why would you do something--
你疯了吗  你为什么要这么做
Mike has asked me to marry him.
麦克让我嫁给他
What?
什么
And i was afraid that if he found out
我怕  他如果知道
That you weren't really in love with jackson,
你不是真心和杰克逊相爱
That he might change his mind about me.
他可能会改变对我的心意
Okay, katherine, that is...
凯瑟琳  这...
It's totally unfair to mike.
对麦克不公平
I mean, he needs to know the truth.
我是说  他应该知道真相
I can make him happy, susan.
我能给他幸福  苏珊
He just needs to get over you.
他需要时间淡忘你
Katherine?
凯瑟琳
Please, don't ruin this.
别毁了这一切
Hey, you wanna just order in?
你是不是要...
Oh, hey, susan.
苏珊  你好
Um... I'm glad you're here.
很高兴你在这儿
Um, I have something I wanna tell you.
我有些话要跟你说
Um, yeah. I...
是  我
Katherine already told me about your big news.
凯瑟琳已经跟我说了  你们的喜事
Well, hope we have your blessing.
希望能得到你的祝福
Yes, sure.
没问题
Why not?
应该祝福
I'm sorry, susan.
抱歉  苏珊
I was gonna tell you myself.
我应该亲口对你说的
Well, don't be mad at katherine.
别怪凯瑟琳
We all know that she just can't... keep a secret.
我们都知道  她守不住秘密
wow, this place is looking worse than ever
这里看起来比以前糟糕许多
Yeah, Aunt Connie's Salons haven't been doing so well.
康妮姨妈的沙龙看上去有点寒酸
maybe you should take off some of those diamonds.
也许你该少戴点钻石饰品
You walk in there like that,
你这么走进去  就像
You're gonna make her feel bad about herself.
在刺激她更加自惭形秽
Say no more.
那还用说
You know, Aunt Connie's like a second mother to me.
康妮姨妈就像我的亲妈一样
Why do you hat her so much?
你为什么这么讨厌她
because all she ever does is put me down.
因为她一直贬低我
If you'd pay attention, you'd see what I'm talking about.
稍加注意  就能看出来
Oh! There's my Carlos!
卡洛斯来了
Are these the girls?
这两个是你女儿
No! they're so grown up!
都长这么大了
And, Gaby...
加布
Is it just me,
只有我这么觉得吗
Or do you get more beautiful every time I see you?
每次看到你  你都越来越漂亮了
No, it's not just you.
不是只有你觉得
Come here. Give me a hug.
过来  给我个拥抱
Let me see your palms.
先让我看看你手脏不脏
- Gaby.
-加布
Fine.
好吧
Now come on in!
快进来吧
The whole family's here.
整个家族都来了
And I've mad some of my world-famous tamales.
我还做了我远近驰名的玉米粽子
Aunt Connie seems nice.
康妮姨妈看上去人很好
Maybe she's changed.
也许她已有所改变了
Trash don't change, sweetheart. She's up to something.
本性难移  宝贝  她肯定有所求
Now come on, let's go grab a lawn chair
过来  在草坪上的火蚁咬人之前
Before we get stuck on the grass with the fire ants.
我们得先去抢把好椅子坐
Tom Scavo, this is Mr. Cummings.
汤姆·斯加沃  我是卡明斯
We met during your tour of the campus.
我们在学校里会过面
Forgive me,
请原谅
But I gave you the wrong date for the admissions test.
我给你的入学考试时间有错
It's tomorrow at 8 a.m.
应该是明早8点
So get a good night's sleep,
所以睡个好觉
And we'll see you first thing in the morning.
明天一早见
Help! help! help! help! Oh!
来帮下忙
Coming. I'm coming.
来了  我来了
It goes... there.
这个放那儿
So I was thinking this whole going back to school thing
关于你重返校园这件事  我想了下
Deserves a little celebration.
我们该小小地庆祝下
Really? I didn't think you were on board.
真的  我还以为你并不赞成
I wanna be supportive.
我想支持你
Let's go for a nice dinner,
我们去美餐一顿
Get a bottle of wine...
上瓶好酒...
Maybe two, since we don't have to wake up early tomorrow.
既然明天不用早起  也许喝个两瓶好了
Or we can go to that Mexican place
或者  我们可以去那家墨西哥餐馆
That has those great margaritas.
他们的玛格丽塔酒太棒了
Oh, Tom. you and tequila?
汤姆  龙舌兰可是烈性酒
What a great idea.
真是好主意
Okay, everybody, I need you to gather around.
大家注意了  围成一个圈
Aunt Connie has something to say.
康妮姨妈有话要说
Gaby, come on. Here's waiting.
加布  来  就等你了
Well, let her wait. I need something to drink.
让她等等吧  我得找点喝的
Trying to keep down one of her's world-famous tamales
帮我咽下她那远近驰名的玉米粽子
Thank you all so much for coming today.
非常感谢各位光临
It's been so long since we've been together.
我们太久没有像这样聚在一起了
We love you, Aunt Connie.
康妮姨妈  我们爱你
Oh, and I love all of you.
我也爱你们大家
There's nothing more important than family.
没有什么比家人更重要的了
And now I have an announcement to make.
现在我要宣布一件事
As many of you know,
众所周知
I've battled a weak heart for most of my life.
我心脏不好  此生大部分时间都在与此抗争
And the doctor now tells me
如今  医生告诉我
That I may only have a few months left.
我只剩下没几个月活头了
Sorry.
抱歉
Bad heart. Floor's all yours.
心脏不好  往下说
As some of you know,
有些人可能知道
I've been taking care of my granddaughter,
我一直在照顾着我的孙女
My beautiful Ana.
我漂亮的安娜
Because of my condition, I can't do it anymore,
但因为我目前的状况  我无法抚养下去
And I need someone to take her in.
需要有人能接下这个担子
I realize that this is a lot to ask.
我知道这个要求有点过分
We would love to help out
我们本来很高兴能帮上忙的
But Miguel just lost his job.
但米格尔刚刚失业
We're barely scraping by.
我们自己也很困难
I understand.
我能理解
Obviously, it has to be someone who can afford to do this.
显然  得找个能负担得起的
We wish we could, but we've got such a full house.
我们倒希望能帮上忙  但房子住不下了
Maybe it should be someone who doesn't have kids.
也许该找个没孩子的
I know this is not gonna be easy, but we're family,
我知道这不会是简单的事  但我们是家人
And this is what we do for each other.
这就是我们该为彼此做的
Well, you know...
你知道的
We're still gonna be family tomorrow,
明天我们还是家人
So I think we should think about it overnight
所以我觉得我们该好好想上一通宵
And search our hearts,
扪心自问
And try to figure out
好好想想
Which one of your homes is best for Ana.
对安娜来说  哪个家最适合她
Gabrielle's right.
加布丽尔说得对
And please know that I won't judge any of you harshly
还有  你们要知道   如果你们决定不照顾
If you decide that you cannot take care
我不会怪你们的
Of my beautiful granddaughter.
我那漂亮的孙女
We love you, Aunt Connie!
康妮姨妈  我们爱你
What are you doing?
你在做什么
I'm helping.
在帮忙
I don't need any help.
我不需要你帮忙
And besides, my parisian salad doesn't call for any chives.
再说  我的巴黎特色沙拉也不需要放葱
Yes. I've always thought it was a bit bland.
是的  我一直觉得那样太清淡了
I think the chives will give it
我觉得香葱能给它带来点
the bite it's so sortly lacking
它一向缺少的刺激食欲的感觉
My salad has plenty of bite.
我做的沙拉本来就刺激食欲
So... when are you moving out?
你准备什么时候搬出去
Acally, I'm not.
事实上  我不会搬的
Excuse me?
你说什么
Oh, I've decided to stay so we can work on our marriage.
我决定留下来  一起为我们的婚姻再努力一把
Am I cutting these too fine?
瞧我不是切得很好吗
Orson, I understand this is a shock,
奥森  我理解你之前受惊
But you have to face facts. Our marriage is over.
但你必须面对现实  我们的婚姻已经完了
Ah, once you weigh what's at stake,
一旦你衡量了利益攸关
I think you'll change your mind.
我想你会改变主意的
Well, if you're referring to the financial settlement,
如果你指的是财务清算的问题
I already told you, I don't care anymore.
我跟你说过了  我什么都无所谓了
No, actually, I'm referring to your freedom.
不  事实上  我指的是你的自由
I've been to jail, Bree.
我坐过牢  布里
Trust me, you wouldn't last ten seconds.
相信我  你连一刻都无法忍受
- Jail?
-坐牢
Yes, of course.
是的  当然
Well, insurance fraud is a serious crime.
保险欺诈可是重罪
ah, but I never filed insurance crime.
但我从来没申请过保险理赔
Ah, but I did.
但我申请了
- What?!
-什么
Yes, I thought we were robbed.
是的  我以为我们被抢了
So, of course,
所以  理所当然的
I did the responsible thing and reported it...
我做了我该做的  上报了
On both our behalves.
我们两个人的财产损失
And since you rather carelessly
由于你非常不小心地
Rented the storage unit under your own name,
用你自己的名字租下了仓库
I think the police will find me completely blameless.
我觉得警察会认为我是无辜的
You would actually send your wife to prison?
你真的想把你妻子送进监狱
My wife? No.
我妻子  不
My ex-wife? You bet.
我前妻  你说呢
But it won't come to that, darling.
但亲爱的  没有那么糟的
I know we can get back to what we both once had.
我知道我们还能重拾美好的时光
That will never happen.
不会让你得逞
And sure we've had our challenges--
当然  前路还有很多挑战
Your penchant for emasculation, my kleptomania.
你的性冷淡  我的盗窃癖
But every marriage has its ebb and flow.
但家家有本难念的经
Orson, please don't do this.
奥森  请你别这样
I don't love you.
我不再爱你了
That's all right, darling.
没关系的  亲爱的
I have enough love for the both of us.
我一个人的爱就足够我们俩用了
Not bland anymore.
不再清淡无味了
The girls are sacked out. Can we talk now?
孩子们都睡了  我们能谈谈吗
What's there to talk about?
还有什么好谈的
You won't even let the girls get a golden retriever,
孩子们想要个金毛犬你都不让
And now you wanna take in a teenager?
现在你想带个十几岁的孩子回来
It's not about what I want
这不是我想做什么的问题
It's about doing the right thing.
是选择做正确的事
This is what family does for each other.
这是家人能为彼此做到的
well, luckily, it'a big family
幸运的是  你有个大家族
Let her go live with Nina and Luis.
让她跟着妮娜和路易斯好了
They have eight kids.
他们已经有8个孩子了
So what's one more?
再多一个也无所谓了
They'll never know the difference.
他们都感觉不出差别来
You're being selfish.
你这么做太自私了
No, I'm thinking about our children.
不  我是在为我们自己的孩子们着想
They're so happy.
她们现在过得很幸福
Taking in a kid we don't even know? That's a huge risk.
带个陌生孩子回来  那太冒险了
Yeah, it's the same risk
是啊  当年康妮姨妈
My aunt Connie took for me and my mother.
接纳我和我妈的时候也一样在冒险
my father left, my mum and I had nowhere else to turn.
我爸走了之后  我和我妈无处投靠
Aunt Connie opened her home to us.
康妮姨妈把我们接到她家
She saved us from the streets.
让我们不至于流落街头
yeah, and knowing Aunt Connie
是啊  以我对康妮姨妈的了解
She's waited all these years to call that favor in.
她等了这么多年  就等你回报她了
She's probably dying on purpose.
她很有可能是故意要死的
Babe, we are so blessed.
宝贝  我们如此受上天眷顾
This is a chance for us to give back.
这是我们回报的机会
Maybe God gave me back my sight and all this money
也许  上帝让我重新得到我的视力和财富
So I could help my family.
就是为了让我帮助我的家人
Gaby, think about it.
加布  设想一下
If something happened to us,
如果我们有任何不测
Wouldn't you want someone to do this for our two girls?
你想不想有人来帮助下我们的孩子
Okay, whoa, whoa, easy. you're a little drunk there.
放轻松  你有点醉了
That's 'cause I love you, Lynette!
那是因为我爱你  勒奈特
I love you, too, baby. Here you go.
我也爱你  宝贝  你来接手
And I love you, Preston.
我也爱你  普雷斯顿
I'm Porter.
我是波特
I could never tell you two apart.
我从来没分清过你们俩
But you're my favorite.
但你是我的最爱
Lynette!
勒奈特
How come you let me drink so many margaritas?
你怎么会让我喝这么多玛格丽特
Yeah, and why did we have to stay till closing?
为什么我们非得在那待到他们打烊
- It's almost 2.
-都快凌晨两点了
Who cares what time it is?
无所谓什么时间了
We were celebrating a big change in your dad's life.
我们在庆祝你爸生命中的重大转折
Hey, someone called.
有个电话留言
Tom Scavo, this is Mr. Cummings.
汤姆·斯加沃  我是卡明斯
We met during your tour of the campus.
我们在学校里会过面
Forgive me,
请原谅
But I gave you the wrong date for the admissions test.
我给你的入学考试时间有错
It's tomorrow at 8 a.m.
应该是明早8点
Oh, cram! I gotta crap for that test!
糟糕  我的考试肯定玩完了
Oh,Jeezs.
天哪
Dr.Heller,Please contact me inmediately.Claire
海勒医生  请马上跟我联系  克莱尔
They're on to you.
他们在找你
Those messages you sent to my receptionist
你发给我们前台的消息
Didn't fool anybody.
骗不了任何人
They've identified my body,
他们已经鉴定我的尸体
And now they're trying to trap you.
现在  他们准备设陷抓住你
It's not gonna work.
没有用的
They can trace those signals, Dave.
大卫  他们能追踪着那些线索
They're going to find you.
然后  他们就会找到你
It's too late.
太迟了
Whatever plan you had,
不管你又在计划什么
It went to hell when you killed me.
在你杀了我的时候  就全盘失效了
You should've stayed on your meds.
你该清醒地认识到这点
Y-you don't know what you're talking about.
谁知道你在胡扯些什么
I'm getting away with this.
我能蒙混过去的
Why would you want to?
你为什么想蒙混过去
I don't mean to criticize,
不是我想吹毛求疵
But I thought you were doing this for us.
但我以为你做这些  都是为了我们
I am.
我是的
I want justice for our family.
我想为我的家人讨回公平
Then who cares if you're caught?
那你会不会被抓  又有什么关系呢
We miss you, Dave.
我们很想你  大卫
We should be together.
我们该待在一起
So...
所以
What are you saying?
你的意思是
So I should just... walk over and kill M.J. now?
我该直接走过去  现在就杀了MJ
Sure. Why not?
当然  为什么不
And let's face it, your plan to take the kid to some lake
好好想想  你计划把那孩子带到湖边
And pretend he accidtally drowned?
制造他失足落水的假象
Boring.
无聊透顶
Hey, isn't it better than Susan know
直接让苏珊知道
Why her son had to die?
为什么她儿子该死不是更好吗
I mean, the whole point is to make her suffer.
我是说  重点在于让她活受罪
Right?
对吗
That's true.
是的
And then the whole world will finally understand
然后  全世界都会明白
What you've been going through.
你经历过怎样的苦难
Yeah, that's it! Good job.
是的  就是这样  做得好
One more just like that.
再投一次这样的
Ooh. hey. um, can i talk to you a sec?
我能和你谈谈吗
Yeah. sure.
行啊
I'm gonna get some juice. you want anything?
我去倒点果汁喝  你要喝点什么
Um, no, thanks.
不用了  谢谢
So, look, uh..
我想说...
I'm sorry if i was
那天你们告知我
A little under-enthusiastic the other day
你们要结婚  我表现得很冷淡
About you and katherine getting married.
对此我表示抱歉
Oh, well, i understand.
没关系  我理解
You just found out your fiance was being deported.
你发现  你的未婚夫被别人抢走了
The timing kind of sucked.
失去了才知道珍惜
Yeah. that and, uh...
是啊  在那之后...
I don't know. it d-did kind of come out of nowhere.
我不清楚  仿佛有种后来者居上的感觉
Well, we have been living together.
我们曾经一起生活过
I know.
我知道
But still... i mean, it happened so fast.
不过  对我来说还是太突然了
I just...
我只是...
I wanna make sure that you know what you're doing.
我只是想确定 你真的知道你在做什么吗
Susan...
苏珊
I know. and feel free to throw me out of your house
我懂  把我赶出去  感到很自由是吗
If i'm out of line...
我是不够好
But do you love her?
但你真的爱她吗
Why would you ask that?
你为什么这么问
Just answer the question.
回答我
Yeah.
爱
I love her.
我爱他
Good.
好吧
That's all i needed to hear.
这就是我想听的
Well, i hope that you will be very happy together.
那么  祝你们幸福
And i hope everything works out for you and jackson.
我也祝你和杰克逊一切都好
Yeah, well, i don't know if that's gonna happen.
谢谢  但我不知道会不会一切都好
What do you mean? you two aren't getting married?
什么意思  你们还没结婚吗?
Oh, the truth is, um...
事实上...
Well, it's complicated.
这件事很复杂
Hey, susan!
苏珊
M.j. told me you're here. what are you guys talking about
M.J.告诉我你在这  你们谈什么呢?
We were talking about you, actually.
其实  我们在谈你
Me? what about me?
我   能和我说说吗
Well...
恩...
I realized that i never properly congratulated you
我突然发现  我从没好好地祝贺过你
On getting married.
新婚快乐
Really?
真的吗
Really.
真的
Hey, babe. how'd the test go?
亲爱的  测试结果如何
It's as though...
结果就像
I dug down deep
我挖了个很深的坑
And i found a new level of suck
之后发现还得再挖一个  该死的
That i never knew i had in me.
我从没有过这种感觉
I'm sure it wasn't that bad.
没有那么糟糕吧
Lynette...
勒奈特
I puked tequila in the parking lot,
我喝醉了  然后在停车场吐了
I-i passed out twice in the essay section,
前两次笔试我都过了
i giggled uncontrollably when i read the word "uranus."
但当我看到"uranus"这个词时  我实在憋不住笑了
Add to that that i'm pretty sure
接下来  我敢肯定
that i spelled "scavo" wrong
我把 "scavo" 拼错了
And it is a safe bet that i will not be
我打赌  我以后再不会
Broadening my horizons anytime soon.
胡乱拓展兴趣领域了
Don't sweat it.
别放弃
You wanted to learn chinese...
学汉语是你的理想...
Mm, we'll get you a book.
我给你拿本书
Mandarin is a very complicated language.
汉语普通话真难学啊
You can't get the kind of fluency you need
你永远不能从一本书里
For the professional marketplace from a book.
学一口流利的商务用语
Marketplace?
商务用语
That's the whole point.
这才是重点
China is one of the world's fastest growing economies.
中国是世界上经济发展最快的国家之一
the opportunity for someone with my marketing experience
现在有个机会  以我的市场经验
Who can speak the language are amazing.
如果还会说中文  那就太好了
I mean, we're talking beaucoup bucks.
我的意思是  我们在谈一宗大生意
I could've totally reinvented myself.
我早就该改造下自己了
That's...
那可真是
A brilliant plan.
一个辉煌的计划
Why didn't you tell me this?
你怎么不早点告诉我
What does matter?
早点说又能怎样
It's over.
机会没了
I'm sorry i let you down.
对不起  让你失望了
You're getting married this weekend?
你们这周末结婚是吗
Yeah. that's the good thing about vegas.
是啊  拉斯维加斯是个好地方
Doesn't require any planning. oh, my gosh.
一点也不需要我们作准备  哦  天啊
You know what? why don't you come with us?
你跟我们一起去吧
You could be my maid of honor.
你可以做我的伴娘
That's ridiculous, isn't it?
很荒谬  是吧
It's sweet, but...
是个好主意 不过
Yeah, it's ridiculous.
确实很荒谬
And besides,m,
而且
M.j. and i have big plans this weekend.
M.J. 和我  这个周末有个大计划
Hey, dave.
大卫
Glad i caught you.
真巧见到你
Is your friend's boat still available this weekend?
你朋友的船这周末有空吗
What?
什么
i was thinking about what you said, and you were right.
我考虑了一下你跟我说的计划  你是对的
It really would do me good to
离开这出去玩几天
get out of here for a few days
对我很有好处
You're right.
说的对
It would do us all some good.
对我们都有好处
Carlos!
卡洛斯
You have no idea how much this means to me,
无法想象  这对我有多重要
Knowing that you and gaby
当我知道  你和加布
Will be looking after my beautiful ana.
将会照顾我漂亮的小安娜
I can finally be at peace.
我放心多了
I love you, too.
我也爱你
And tell gaby i said thank you.
告诉加布我万分感谢
Bye.
再见
So... are you gonna tell him the truth about ana?
你准备告诉他关于安娜的真相吗
Oh, they'll find out soon enough.
他们迟早会发现的
Hello?
喂
Hi. i'm trying to reach roberta simmonds.
你好  请问萝伯塔.赛蒙在吗
Speaking, but barely. who's this?
正是我  但请问  你是谁
This is claire cormier,
我是科莱尔.考米艾
Dr. heller's receptionist.
海勒医生的接待员
Do you remember me?
还记得我吗
Yeah, sure
是的  还记得
But i'm right in the middle of my breakfast,
但我正享用我的早膳
so could you call me back around 11:00
能不能到11点再打来
i just thought you might wanna know
有些事你可能感兴趣
The police stopped by.
警察来过了
They told me that dr. heller is dead.
他们说海勒医生死了
Yeah, go on. i'm listening.
请继续  我洗耳恭听
Dr. heller died in a fire at the white horse?
海勒医生不是在白马俱乐部被烧死的吗
And apparently, there was no smoke in his lungs.
但很明显  在他肺部没有发现烟熏迹象
Which means he was dead before the fire started.
也就是说  他在火灾发生前就死了
My guess the person he was coming to see
依我拙见  当时的凶手
is the person who killed him.
就是他前来拜访的对象
- Dave.
-大卫
Dave
是大卫
- Roberta, what are we gonna do?
-萝伯塔  下一步怎么办
go to the police.
去报警
And tell 'em what?
跟他们说什么
We know dr.heller was a criminal scycologist
我们已确定海勒医是个犯罪心理学家
And we're pretty sure dave was his patient.
同样也可以肯定  大卫就是他的病人
I'd feel better if we had proof.
要是有证据就好了
I'd feel better if i had a functioning liver,
要是我们在他家有间谍那岂不更好
But sometimes you have to play the hand you're dealt.
但有时你必须亲力亲为
If we walk into the police with a half-cocked story,
要是我们去跟警察说一个只有半截的故事
They're gonna laugh us out of the station.
会被他们笑死的
I don't know how,
我不知道应该
But we--we gotta give 'em something more.
应该如何去获得更多线索
Didn't you tell me dave once broke into your house?
你不是跟我说过  大卫有一回闯入你家吗
Yeah. why?
是的  怎么了
Maybe it's time we returned the favor.
或许是时候以牙还牙了
You know, when you missed your appointment on monday,
周一跟你约好了  你没来
We thought maybe you skipped out on us.
我们想你是否逃走了
Yeah, well, as you can see, i was otherwise detained.
是啊  正如你所见  我被捕了
You know this guy?
你认识这个人么
No.
不认识
Who is he?
他是谁
Samuel heller--the john doe who died in the club fire.
塞缪尔·海勒  他在俱乐部火灾中丧生
You sure you didn't see him when
你确定那天在俱乐部的后台
you were in that back away
没有见过这个人吗
No.
不
Well, like i told you that night,
就像那晚我告诉你的
I was only back there for a minute.
我只是在后台待了一会儿
And you didn't see anybody?
你也没见到别人
Aw, jeez, it was a long time ago.
老天  真的过了很久了
No. i was looking for the men's room.
我正想找男厕所
I ran into dave williams.
看到大卫·威廉姆斯
He was coming out of the storage room--
他正好从储藏室出来
Wait. you saw dave williams come out of the storage room
等等  你说你见到大卫·威廉姆斯从储藏室出来
Yeah.
是的
Didn't i tell you that before?
难道以前没告诉过你们吗
I thought it was the bathroom,
我以为那是洗手间
But dave pointed me in the right direction.
大卫告诉我应该往右转
And right after that, somebody locked you in.
于是  有人把你反锁在里面
Come on. you don't think dave did that.
拜托  你们不会以为是大卫干的吧
I don't know. he have any reason to harm you?
不知道  他有动机来害你吗
No.
没有
We're friends.
我们是好朋友
He's one of the nicest guys i've ever met.
他是我见过的最善良的人
Well, thank you for your time, mr. braddock.
谢谢你抽时间  布拉多克先生
I'm sorry i couldn't be more help.
对不起  没帮上什么忙
How many times we talk to this williams guy?
这个叫威廉姆斯的我们讨论过几次
Oh, i don't know. four?
不记得了  4次
He ever mention anything about be in that storage room
他从未提起他在储藏室待过
He did not.
的确没有
And i'm gonna catch a fish this big.
我要钓一条这么大的鱼
Well, if you do, we're gonna clean it
真钓到的话  我们就把它洗干净
And serve it up for dinner.
用来做晚餐
and if i don't, can we eat the worms
要是没钓着  是否只能吃饵虫了
Just make sure he catches a fish.
务必让他钓到大鱼
Hey, mike, i got something for you.
麦克  有东西给你
It's a video from our band, one of our early rehearsals.
是我们乐队的录影  一场早期的演出
Man, do i even want to see this?
还有必要看吗
Yeah. we weren't half bad.
我们不赖的
Don't watch it till you get back from your honeymoon. ok?
但蜜月回来前  千万别看  行吗
Will do. thanks.
照办  谢了
Okay.
好了
Bye, mike.
再见  麦克
Have a nice wedding.
新婚愉快
Thanks.
谢谢
You take good care of my boy, okay?
好好照顾我儿子  好吗
Three years ago
三年前
The first thing Lila Dash thought about
死神降临的清晨
That fateful morning was her husband Dave.
莱拉·黛西醒来想到的第一个人是丈夫大卫
It occurred to her she should buy him a new tie.
她想给他买条新领带
She thought of her husband again that afternoon...
那天下午她又想到丈夫
decided she would make him something special for dinner.
她想为他做一顿丰盛的晚餐
That evening, lila once again thought about her husband...
傍晚  她再次想到丈夫
And she asked herself what she had done
她自问是何神眷顾
To deserve someone
给了她一个
So wonderful.
如此完美的丈夫
Hey, you. what are you thinking about?
你在想什么呢
Nothing.
没什么
So what do you say we all go out for ice cream?
我们去吃冰淇淋吧
Oh, i'd love to, but i brought work home.
我很想去  不过我还得工作
Again?
又是工作
I know. i'm so boring.
是啊  无聊至极
Hey, why don't you two go?
要不你俩去吧
No. we'll all go tomorrow.
算了吧  明天我们一块去
Now how can you make this face
你怎能忍心让小可爱渴望了一天
wait a whole day
却吃不到冰淇淋
Look sad.
装得伤心点
Yeah. oh!
对  就这样
Oh, fine.
好吧
I'll take her now.
我这就带她去
Come on, sweetie.
走吧  亲爱的
Hey, how about tomorrow night,
明晚怎么样
I'll leave my briefcase at the office,
明天保证不把工作带回家
And we do something special, just the three of us?
我们去玩点开心的  就我们仨
It's a date.
说话算数
But there would be no tomorrows for Lila and Paige Dash...
但没人知道她们的生命即将终结
Because that was the night they crashed...
因为那晚她们出了车祸
Into Susan and Mike delfino.
撞上了苏珊和麦克·德尔非诺的车
The last thing Lila Dash thought about before she died
莱拉·黛西在生命终结那刻
Was her husband Dave.
脑中依然是丈夫大卫
She wondered what her death would do to him.
她不知道丈夫会如何接受如此浩劫
Luckily for Lila,
莱拉是幸运的
She would never know.
她再也不会知道了
更多字幕  请访问 http://www.yyets.net/
本字幕由人人影视荣誉出品
校对：小门柴
翻译：桃金娘银  小天天鱼  Joanna  祭司
总监：小门柴
时间轴：娅娅  Sadnessleaf
There was a wedding recently
最近  在美景镇的长老会教堂里
At fairview presbyterian church.
有一场盛大的婚礼
The minister spoke about the nature of marriage
牧师宣读婚姻的本质
And then said what all ministers say
然后他像所有的牧师一样
To conclude such matters.
做了最后的结语
You may now kiss the bride.
你可以吻新娘了
It was then the church bells began to ring,
这时教堂钟声开始响起
Telling brides-to-be everywhere
告诉各地的准新娘们
Their turn was next.
下一个就是她们了
Hello, groom.
好啊  新郎
Guess what?
知道吗
I called the hotel to tell them we were getting married.
我给酒店打了电话  并告诉他们我们快就要结婚了
They promised to upgrade us to a suite
他们答应把我们的房间升级为套房
And have champagne on ice.
还有冰镇香槟
- Isn't that terrific? yeah.
-很棒吧
Yeah, that's great.
对  很棒
Wow, i hope you can muster up a little more enthusiasm
我希望你在说"我愿意"时
For the "i dos."
能比现在更激情一些
I'm sorry. I'm just thinking about Susan and M.J.
抱歉  我只是在想苏珊和M.J.
Why?
为什么
Well, when they left, i just got a weird vibe from dave.
当他们出发的时候  感觉大卫怪怪的
Dave always gives off a weird vibe. that's just dave.
这就是大卫  他总是让别人觉得很奇怪
No, i-i think i should call 'em.
不  我应该打个电话给他们
Or maybe you should get our bags in the car
或许你应该把行李放进车里
So we don't miss our flight? because if we miss our flight,
我们就不会误了飞机  因为要是误了航班
We're going to miss our wedding day,
我们就会误了婚礼
And if we miss our wedding day,
如果误掉婚礼
We're gonna miss our wedding night.
我们将会误掉新婚夜
Yeah, you're right.
好  我听你的
I'm probably worried about nothing. I'll load the car.
可能我是杞人忧天了  我这就去把东西装上车
Uh, we need to stop at the store.
我们需要在商店那里停一下
I have to get videotape for the camera.
我得买摄影带
oh, i got some old
我有一些用过的
Just grab one. we'll record over it.
拿一个  在上面重录就行了
She's two blocks away. she'll be here any second.
还有两个街口远  她马上就到了
Great.
太好了
Are you nervous?
紧张吗
Why would i be nervous?
为什么我要紧张
Well, you're about to have a teenager in the house.
家里会来一个少女
Well, i didn't say i wasn't sedated.
我没说过我很平静
Yeah, i'm a little freaked out, too.
对  我也有点紧张
But we're doing the right thing.
但我们在做好事
Yeah, when i think about everything
是啊  当我想到那个小女孩
That little girl's been through...
经历过的事情
Her dad walked out, her mother's in jail,
父亲离开了她  母亲又进了监狱
The way she bounced from relative to relative--
家人把她踢来踢去
- I just want this to be the end of the line for her.
-我希望这就是她的归属了
Me, too.
我也是
Mommy, here comes the taxi!
妈妈  来了辆计程车
I wonder if she'll even remember me.
不知道她还记得我吗
Oh, i doubt it. you haven't seen her since she was 6.
可能不记得了  她6岁后你就没有再见过她了
Yeah, and when she was little, i used to spend a lot of time
当她很小  爸爸没去世前  我常常和他俩
With her and her dad before he left.
在一起玩
I remember taking her on the swings at the park.
我记得带她去公园荡秋千
I remember buying her ice cream.
给她买冰淇淋
I remember giving her piggyback rides. ohh.
还有让她骑在我肩上
I don't remember that.
感觉印象不深了
You told him about the divorce?
你告诉他要和他离婚
I had to. He found the storge unite
我没得选  他发现存储室了
He wanted an explanation.
他要我解释
I was in such a state of shock,
我当时被吓坏了
I couldn't think of anything else to say.
不知道还能说什么
- Bree, this isn't good.
-布里  这对你不利
You have no idea.
你不了解情况
Now he's saying if i try to divorce him,
现在他说如果我要和他离婚
He can go to the police and report me.
他就去警局告发我
-Report you? for what?
-告发?  告发什么
Filing a false insurance claim.
骗取保险金
He's the one who filed it,
那是他干的
But he's gonna say that i told him to.
但他会说是我怂恿他做的
- crap.
-变态
I told him i don't love him. he said he doesn't care
我说我不爱他了  他说他不在乎
He wants us to work on our marriage.
他想拯救我们的婚姻
Oh, wow. well, clearly, the guy's a little crazy.
哦  显然他有点不正常了
A little? the man put chives in my parisian salad!
有点  他在我巴黎沙拉里放香葱
He should be in a straightjacket!
他应该被送进疯人院的
Okay, calm down. This isn't the end of the world.
冷静点  这不是世界末日
Isn't it?
不是吗
I'm being blackmailed by a man i'm starting to despise,
勒索我的人  是我鄙视的人
And if i don't pretend to love him,
我若不假装爱他
He can have me arrested.
他能让警察抓我走
Bree...
布里
I don't want you to worry about this.
这点我想你不必担心
We're gonna think of something.
我们会有办法的
What can we think of? he's holding all the cards.
我们还能做什么  我的把柄全在他手上
Trust me. no one ever holds allthe cards.
相信我  谁也不能抓住所有的把柄
Lynette, get down here!
勒奈特  快下来
- What's going on?
-发生什么事了
I just got off
我刚接到
the phone with university
大学打来的电话
I'm in!
我被录取了
Really?! you passed the test?!
真的  你通过考试了
Not only did i pass the test,
不仅是通过
Your genius husband scored in the top 5%,
你天才丈夫考进了前5%
Drunk out of his mind!
难以置信
Which, by the way, i am not condoning... ever.
顺便说一句  我从未如此幸运  从来没有
Congrats, dad!
祝贺你  爸爸
Thank you, baby. mwah!
宝贝  谢谢你
I can help you study if you want.
如果你愿意我能在学习上帮帮你
I'm not sure how much help you're gonna be.
我不知道你能不能帮我
I'm majoring in chinese.
我主修的可是汉语
I know how to say "take me to a strip bar" in mandarin.
我知道怎么用普通话讲"我要去脱衣俱乐部"
I'm so proud.
我很自豪
Porter, aren't you gonna congratulate your father?
波特  你不向你父亲表示一下祝贺吗
Congratulations on ruining my life.
恭喜你毁掉我的人生
If you see me on campus,
如果你在校园里看见我
You're not allowed to talk to me.
请当作不认识我
Okay, that's everyone.
好的  每个人都恭喜过了
This calls for hot fudge sundaes.
请你们吃热巧克力圣代
Everybody... in the car!
上车吧
- You coming?
-你也去吗
I'm gonna make a quick phone call,
我得打一个电话
- And i'll be right out.
-马上就来
Okay.
好的
Hi. this is lynette scavo.
你好  我是勒奈特·斯加沃
May i please speak to Dr. Rushton?
请找一下拉西顿医生
Tell him it's important.
告诉他很紧急
Hi. Dr. Rushton,
你好  拉西顿医生
I need to come in and see you as soon as possible.
我想尽快来做一下检查
I think the cancer's back.
好像癌症又复发了
Mommy, can i have a juice box?
妈妈  我能再要一盒桔汁吗
Oh, sweetie. you just had one,
宝贝儿  你不是刚刚才喝过吗
And we don't want to have to stop ten times
我们可不想一路上不断停车
So you can go to the bathroom.
等你上厕所
I miss diapers.
我想念我的尿布
Oh, the joys of being a parent.
这就是做父母的乐趣
Yeah, i remember.
对啊  我知道
You do?
你知道吗
I had a little girl.
我有过一个女儿
She died.
她死了
Oh, my God. I...
我的上帝  我
I-I had no idea. i'm so sorry.
抱歉  我不知该怎么说
That's okay.
没事
I'm learning to deal with it.
我在学着慢慢习惯
I can't believe edie gave you a key
伊迪居然给你钥匙
Why not? she trusted me
为什么不呢  她信任我
And i only used it when i was out of milk or bread...
只有在牛奶面包吃光的情况我才用
Or cash.
还有现金
Okay, look for anything that could tie Dave to Dr. Heller.
找找能把大卫和海勒医生联系起来的一切东西
Look through his files, his papers, even his trash.
检查他的文件  资料  包括垃圾
Roberta, what are you doing?
萝伯塔  你在做什么
- We're trying to catch a murderer.
-我们来查杀人犯的
I know,
我知道
but before i get to the bottom of that
但在查清楚前
I'd like to get to the bottom of this.
我得先把这个喝掉
Oh, look!
快看
Oh! muscle relaxers--score!
肌肉松弛剂  太棒了
Put that back! they're not yours.
放回去  这不是你的
Yeah, apparently, they're not his either. who's david dash?
很明显  也不是他的  大卫·黛西是谁
Mr. williams? it's the police.
威廉姆先生  我们是警察
Oh! oh, cheese it!
快蹲下
We need to ask you a few questions.
我们有几个问题要问你
Please tell me
告诉我
You doesn't have anything illegal on you
你没犯过法吧
I do, but it's hidden
有过  但不易发现
And if they find it, we got a lawsuit.
如果他们一旦发现  我们会被起诉
Ladies?
女士们
Open up, please.
请开门
Uh, hi there. can I help you?
你好  有什么要帮忙的吗
Well, I hope so. are you orson hodge?
是的  你是奥森·霍吉吗
Yes, I am. you are...
对  我是  你哪位
You want me to let go?
你想让我放手吗
Yeah.
对
There, I let go.
看  我放手了
- Now you gotta do the same
-现在你也要放手
I don't know what you mean
我不知道你什么意思
Oh, I think you do, and I am dead serious.
我想你明白我的意思  我是来真的
If you don't let go...
如果你再不放手
Next time, neither will I.
下次  我也不会放手了
Brought you a laundry basket.
给你拿来一个洗衣篮
You need me to show you how to use the washer?
你要我教你怎么用洗衣机吗
It's my clever way of saying
这是我的一种婉转说法
You're gonna be doing your own laundry.
你要自己洗衣服
Oh. okay.
好
You know, the girls have chores, too.
孩子们都要干家务活
It's how we teach 'em responsibility.
这是教她们如何有责任心
Speaking of which, uh...
说到这个
Cutfew is 10:00 11 on weekends.
门禁平时是10点  周末11点
Does that seem reasonable?
你能接受吗
Sure. no problem.
没问题
This teenager thing isn't so bad.
看来你不算问题少女
So what are my other chores?
那我其他的家务活是什么
Oh, well, not to push my luck,
不是我要求多
But I was thinking you could sweep the front porch
但我想  你要打扫前门廊
And take care of the guest bathroom.
还有清扫客房的洗手间
You got it.
明白了
Oh, that's a pretty dress.
好漂亮的裙子
Oh, my god, it's Versace!
天哪  是范思哲的
Yeah. It's all right.
是啊  还好吧
"all right"? young lady, if you live under my roof,
还好  如果你住在我房子里
You will not disparage versace.
你就不能侮辱范思哲的裙子
Sorry.
对不起
No, I'm just kidding. It was a joke.
不  开玩笑呢
Oh. Funny.
好笑
Well, I guess i'm gonna get started on my laundry.
我想  我该开始洗我衣服了
Vera wang!
薇拉王
Where are you getting all these dresses?
你从哪弄到这些裙子
They were gifts.
都是礼物
You know, from boyfriends.
男朋友们送的
Boyfriends? How many do you have?
男朋友们  你有多少男朋友
Not as many as I used to. I had to make some cutbacks.
没以前多了  我也得减员啊
Yeah, the economy has hit us all.
经济危机对我们都有冲击啊
So...
所以
What kind of boyfriends can afford things like this?
什么样的男朋友能买得起这些衣服
They're college guys
他们是大学生
With rich parents who can pay for everything.
只要家里有钱  任何都买得起
Uh-huh. and so... they give you designer clothes,
他们给你买名牌衣服
And you give them...
你给他们
The pleasure of my company.
我陪他们度过愉快的时光
Yeah. okay, well...
是  好
Don't take this the wrong way,
别想错了
But that's not exactly from the Versace virgin line.
但那些可不是范思哲处女系列
I don't have to do anything.
我不需要做什么
They just have to think I might.
只需要他们觉得  我可能会做什么
Uh-huh, and how long do you think that will last?
这要多长时间
Till 10'clock, 11:00 on the weekends.
到10点  周末11点
Just kidding. It was a joke.
开玩笑呢
Funny.
搞笑哦
Are you all right?
你还好吗
What happened to your shirt?
你衬衫怎么了
Why don't you ask your friend?
怎么不问问你的朋友
The one you hired to assault me.
你雇来打我的那位
You were assaulted?
你被打了吗
Grabbed me by the throat, threw me to the ground
扼住我的喉咙  把我推倒在地上
And told me to "let go."
告诉我  让我放手
Your message came through loud and clear.
我完全明白他想传达的信息
I had nothing to do with that.
我什么都没做
Oh, please.
别装了
Who else would have done it?
还能有谁呢
I don't know.
我不知道
But i swear to you, we may have our differences,
但我发誓  我们可能有些分歧
But i would never hire someone to attack you.
但我绝不会雇人来打你
You have to believe me.
你要相信我
I do.
我信
Forgive me.
抱歉
I should've known you could never hurt me.
我早知道你永远都不会伤害我
I'll stay.
我会留下来
What?
什么
Once I've unpacked, I'll bring
我去从行李里找件新衣服
you my shirt so you can mend it
我把这件拿下来  好让你帮我补好
We're just running to the store, and we'll be back in an bit
我们就去趟商店  一会就回来
Okay. I'll sweep the porch while you're gone.
你们走后  我会打扫前门廊的
If you don't mind
如果你不介意
Will you make sure juanita and celia do their chores, too?
能不能监督胡安妮塔和西利娅  让她们把家务活也干了
Sure thing.
没问题
I got the rest, babe.
我拿其他的吧
All right, I'll see you inside.
好  屋里见
Oh, you're back.
你们回来了
Oh, my god.
天哪
Ana, the house is so clean.
房子好干净啊
Just wanted to do my part.
我做好我的本份而已
Well, how did you get everything down so quickly?
你怎么干得这么快啊
We finished upstairs, ana. anything else you need done?
我们把楼上打扫干净了  安娜  还有其他要做的吗
They wanted to hang out, but I had chores to do,
他们跟我出去玩  但我有家务活
So they insisted on helping me.
所以他们坚持要帮我
Aren't they sweet?
他们人是不是很好
Hey, um, I'm not bragging and I don't recommend it,
我不是吹牛  也不是自卖自夸
But you could so eat out of your downstairs toilet.
但楼下厕所现在干净到  可以在里面用餐了
Okay, boys, thanks for your hard work,
孩子们  谢谢你们干活
But maybe it's time to go home and take a shower...
该回家了  去洗个澡吧
Preferably a cold one.
最好是冷水澡
Bye, preston.
再见  普雷斯顿
- I'm porter.
-我是波特
I'm preston.
我是普雷斯顿
- Oh, you can call me whatever you want.
-你叫我什么都行
All right.
好了
Mommy, it was so cool.
妈咪  太酷了
Ana got the boys to do my chores, too.
安娜让男生们把我的家务活也干了
Did she?
是吗
I wanna learn how to make boys do stuff.
我也想学怎么让男生帮我做事情
Can you teach me?
你能教我吗
Uh, okay, Juanita, go to your room.
胡安妮塔  回房间去
And don't come out until you're 18.
不到18岁  别出来
Is something wrong?
怎么了
Ana, the whole point of chores is that you do them.
安娜  家务活的关键是要你去做家务
You don't bat your eyes and call rent-a-horny-kid.
而不是让你抛个媚眼  勾引一个男孩来帮你干
The house is clean. what do you care how it got that way?
房间干净了  你为何要介意过程
I care about the message it sends to my little girls,
我在意的是  这件事对我小女儿的影响
And I'm starting to care a little
现在我开始有点在意
bit about your tone.
你说话的口气
I am sorry.
抱歉
How do you like your housekeepers to speak to you?
你想让你的佣人怎么跟你说话
And the teenager has finally arrived.
还是问题少女啊
Ana, listen.
安娜  听着
We want you to be part of this family.
我们想接纳你成为家庭一份子
We will love you and support you and take care of you,
我们会爱你  支持你  关心你
But in exchange,
但是  同样地
You will show us a little bit of respect and obey our rules,
你也要对我们表示尊敬  并且遵守我们的规矩
Which means doing your own chores,
这意思是  你要自己干家务
No boys in the house and no more gifts from men.
不要再招男生来家里  也不许跟他们收礼物
I get it now.
我现在明白了
You're jealous.
你嫉妒我
Of what?
嫉妒什么
Of me.
嫉妒我
You're not young anymore.
你不再年轻了
You can't get guys to do things for you,
你也不能让男生帮你做这做那了
And that drives you crazy.
这让你抓狂了
You wanna see crazy?
你想知道什么是疯狂吗
Make one more statement like that,
再说一遍这样的话
And I am throwing your ass out on the street.
我就把你扔到街上去
You care to test me?
你要是不怕就试试
Ana? what's wrong?
安娜  怎么了
I don't know what I did. she wants to kick me out.
我不知道我做了什么  她想把我踢走
So she had a couple boys come over and do her chores.
她只不过叫了几个男孩来家里帮她做家务
You've been doing stuff like that your whole life.
你一直都是这么做的
That's not the point! you didn't hear
这不是重点  你没听见
the way she talked to me
她跟我说话的那个态度
I don't care.
我不在乎
You don't tell
你不能跟
a kid who's been bounced around her whole life
一个没有家的孩子说
That you're gonna throw her out on the street!
你要把她扔到街上去
I didn't tell her that.
我没这么说
I just... kind of threatened to.
我只是  类似于威胁她一下
Bottom line-she is my niece,
不管怎样  她是我外甥女
And she is not going anywhere.
她哪都不去  就留在这
You're the adult, gaby. start acting like it.
你是成年人  加布  成熟点吧
I know this looks bad,
我知道看起来不像好事
But we did what we did for a good reason.
我们这么做是有原因的
Ma'am, you can't break into
夫人们  任何原因  你们都不应该
A person's house for any reason.
非法进入别人的房子
Uh, what if there's a baby inside and there's a fire?
那如果着火  房子里有个婴儿呢
See? everything's not all cut and dry, is it, rookie?
看吧  没有什么是绝对的  是不是  菜鸟
Roberta, don't piss him off.
萝伯塔  别惹他生气
You can't take a club to the head like you used to.
你不能像你以前那样硬碰硬
Okay, I just got off the phone with heller's secretary.
我刚跟海勒的秘书通了电话
David dash was definitely a patient there.
大卫·黛西确实是他的一个病人
Well, that's why we couldn't make the match. mm-hmm.
这就是为什么我们总找不到人
He changed his last name. mm-hmm, and get this.
他把他的姓给改了  看看这个
He's the same guy whose wife and daughter
就是他的妻子女儿
Were killed in that car crash up on Canterbury road
都在坎特伯雷路的车祸中丧生
canterbury road.
坎特伯雷路
I remember that accident.
我知道那起事故
My neighbors mike and susan were in the car that hit 'em.
我的邻居麦克和苏珊开车撞上他们的
Oh, wait. now wait. okay, that's weird.
等等  这很古怪
I mean, why would dave move onto the same street
为什么大卫要搬来
As the people who killed his family?
和撞死他家人的凶手做邻居呢
The doctor has your results. he'll be here in a minute.
医生拿到你的结果了  他一会就进来
Do you know what they are?
你知道是什么结果吧
You'll need to talk to the doctor about that.
你要跟医生谈谈
Come on. I know you know. it's cancer again. am I right?
告诉我吧  我知道你一定知道  癌症复发了  对吗
I honestly don't know.
我真的不知道
Now please, he'll just be a moment.
他马上就来
If it's cancer, and I find out you knew,
如果真的是癌症复发了  而你不告诉我
I won't be dying alone.
我就拉着你一块儿死
Hello, Lynette.
你好  勒奈特
Well, I'm glad you came in. We got the results back,
很高兴你来做检查  我们有结果了
And the test did pick something up.
确实有所发现
So it is the cancer.
所以  真的复发了
Oh, God, I can't go through this again!
天哪  这次我一定挺不过去
No, no, no. It's nothing like that.
不  不  不是这样的
You're pregnant.
你怀孕了
Excuse me?
你说什么
About six weeks or so.
大约六周
Are you sure it's not cancer?
你确定不是癌症复发
Okay, Susan.
行了  苏珊
But when you're out on the boat,
但是上船之后
Make sure you'll put on some sweater
记得一定要多穿点
And on your feet, too. Remember our trip to Mexico?
还有注意脚下  记得我们去墨西哥那次吧
Okay, I'll talk to you guys later.
好的  晚点打给你们
Everything's fine.
一切都好
I don't know what I was worried about.
我不知道在胡乱担心些什么
Are you sure you wanna do this?
你确定你想这么做吗
Do what?
做什么
Go to Vegas, get married.
去拉斯维加斯结婚
I mean, it is a whole weekend away from Susan.
我是说  这意味着整个周末见不到苏珊
Katherine, I told you.
凯瑟琳  我跟你说过了
I just wanted to make sure M.J.was OK
我只是确认下MJ一切都好
Why aren't you still commit it,
干嘛不痛快承认
You're still hung up on her.
你依然牵挂着她
For God sake, are we going to do this again?
看在上帝份上  还要再提起这个话题吗
All I know is, it's our wedding day,
我只知道  今天是我们的大喜之日
And you were in a crappy mood
你却一直心神不宁
Until you talked to your ex-wife.
直到给你前妻打过电话才好
Katherine, I wouldn't be sitting here
凯瑟琳  如果我不想娶你的话
If I didn't want to marry you. okay?
我现在不会坐在这里  好吗
Really?
真的
Really.
Do I need to shout it out in the airport?
需要我在机场大声宣告下吗
- You wouldn't do that.
-你才不会这么做呢
Oh, I will.
我会的
I'll--I'll do whatever I need to,
不管做什么我都愿意
- To prove my love
-来证明我对你的爱
It's ok
好了好了
You convinced me.
我相信你了
I am dying for a Cappuccino. you want one?
我想喝杯卡布奇诺  你要吗
Yeah, I do.
愿意一试
You said it. "I do."
你说了"愿意"了
Can't take it back now.
可不能再收回去了
...should be allowed to just... walk away.
怎么可以就这样...一走了之
I know some people will wonder,
我知道有的人可能会想
Why didn't I just kill Susan?
为什么不杀掉苏珊
But what good would that have done?
但如果那样做有什么好处呢
She'd be dead. There'd be no... suffering.
她会死掉  那样永远不会知道...煎熬的滋味
And to those of you who hate me
因为我夺去无辜男孩生命
Because I took the life of an innocent, young boy,
而憎恨我的人们
I say...
我想说...
Katherine!
凯瑟琳
Excuse me.
打扰一下
That woman I was with me?Tell her I have to go.
看到跟我一起的那位女士  跟她说我得走了
It's an emergency!
情况紧急
Oh, uh, your friend asked me to tell you he had to leave.
你朋友让我告诉你  他得先走了
What?
什么
He said to say he's sorry.
他说他很抱歉
What were you thinking?
你到底想怎么样
First, tell me if it worked,
首先  告诉我效果如何
Then I'll tell you what I was thinking.
然后我再来告诉你我的打算
Don't be glib. Did you hire someone to attack Orson?
别跟我油腔滑调的  你雇人去袭击奥森了
Yes.
是的
Are you insane? Your thug tried to strangle him.
你疯了吗  那歹徒差点勒死他
If he had tried to strangle him, he'd be dead.
如果他真想勒死他  不会留下活口的
Look, Orson had the upper hand in this divorce.
奥森在离婚事件中占了上风
We needed to regain it.
我们得夺回优势
Not by resorting to physical violence
不是用这种暴力手段
I would never have given my permission for that.
我绝不会允许你这么做的
That's why I didn't ask you.
这就是为何我没问你的意见
W-what's your beef here, Bree?
你有什么可抱怨的  布里
My beef is that from the minute I walked into this office,
我不满的是  从我踏进这个办公室的那刻起
You have pulled me deeper and deeper
你就拉着我同流合污
Into your moral cesspool.
让我在道德深渊越陷越深
That is not why I hired you.
那可不是我雇你的原因
Please. That is exactly why you hired me.
拜托  这恰恰正是你雇我的原因
Face it. you were tired of being a good girl.
承认吧  你已经厌倦了当个乖乖女
You knew it was time to play dirty.
你知道该是时候耍点手段了
I wanted to protect what was mine.
我只想保护属于我的东西
You have turned me into someone I don't recognize.
你却把我变得失去了自我
And you've loved every minute of it.
而你享受其中的每分每秒
- No, I haven't.
-不  我没有
Yes, you have!
是的  你有
And so have I.
我也是
Because the truth is,
因为  事实是
I think you're the most fascinating woman
你是我遇到过的
That I have ever met.
最迷人的女性
What?
什么
Karl...
卡尔...
If I have not been clear about how I feel about you,
如果我没表达清楚我对你的感觉
I apologize for any ambiguity.
我为我的含糊其辞表示道歉
Understand this-- I detest you.
这么说你明白吧  我讨厌你
No, you don't. I can see it in your eyes.
不  你没有  你的眼睛告诉我了
You want me to walk over there and pull you up against me
你想让我走到身前  把你拉进我怀中
And kiss you until your knees buckle.
吻你  直到你双腿发软
You're fired.
你被炒了
Good. That keeps this from being a breach of ethics.
很好  那我这么做就不至于违反行业道德
My knees haven't buckled yet.
我的双腿还没有发软
Oh, It's your daddy. Hey, Mike.
你爸打来的  喂  麦克
Hey! Hey, where are you? Are you with Dave?
你们在哪  跟大卫在一起吗
uh, yeah. We are in the car singing.
是啊  我们在车里唱歌来着
All right, Susan, listen to me. Do not react
好了  苏珊  听我说  别让他知道
To what I'm about to tell you.
我要告诉你的话
This sounds really--
听起来真的很...
Susan! Do you understand me?
苏珊  听明白了吗
Okay.
好
Dave's real name is David Dash.
大卫的真名是大卫·黛西
He's the husband of the woman
他是我们在那次事故中
That killed in the accident.
害死的女人的丈夫
- Oh my God!
-我的天哪
Don't react!
别给他看出来
Uh... problem?
有问题吗
Uh... that sucks.
太糟糕了
How could they cancel your flight?
他们怎么能取消你们的航班
All right, you guys are in danger.
你们俩有危险
Just get away from him. Go to a gas station, a store...
快逃开他  躲到加油站  小店...
Anyplace there's people. I'm on my way.
只要是有人的地方  我在赶过去了
Right.
好的
So how long do you think you'll be delayed?
你觉得你们会误点多久
Uh, I'm a half-hour from the lake.
我离湖边还有半小时车程
I'm calling the cops right now. Just get away from him.
我会马上报警  你快想法逃开他
Get out of that car and get away from Dave.
离开那辆车  离大卫远远的
- And you call me the second you do.
-到时候打电话给我
Okay.
好的
Um... well, I hope you get there soon.
希望你们很快到达
Bumped his flight?
没坐上那班飞机吗
- Yeah.
-是啊
Oh, what a drag.
真是糟糕
Okay, from the top.
好了  从头开始唱
Gosh, it feels like we've been driving forever.
天  我们好像开了一整天了
Mm. Maybe we should stretch our legs.
也许该活动活动腿脚了
Ah, we're almost there. Let's keep going.
马上就到了  继续前进吧
Aren't you hungry, though?
那你饿不饿
Maybe there's a restaurant up ahead.
也许前面会有餐馆
I really don't want to stop, Susan.
我真的不想停下来  苏珊
Okay.
好的
It's no big deal.
没什么大不了的
Look what I got for college. I got pens. I got notebooks.
看看我为上学准备了什么  笔  笔记本
Ooh, I got an English to Mandarin dictionary
还有一本英汉字典
'cause you never know
因为你永远不知道
When you might need a...gonggongqiche
可能你随时要坐  "公共汽车"
Oh, and look at this.
还有看看这个
Check it out.
见识一下
They're scented. You wanna smell grape?
这是香水笔  想闻闻葡萄的味道吗
What? They're...
干嘛  他们闻起来...
Like candy.
就像糖一样
I went to the doctor today.
我今天去看医生了
What's wrong?
出什么事了
I'm pregnant.
我怀孕了
Pregnant?
怀孕
With a baby?
怀了个孩子
How long have you been sniffing those markers?
闻那记号笔把你脑子闻坏了吗
Of course with a baby.
当然是怀孩子
But you can't. I mean... w-we can't.
但是你不能  我是说  我们不能...
W-we're old!
我们都老了
Well, apparently, not old enough.
很显然  还不够老
What am I gonna do about school?
那我上学的事怎么办
What am I gonna do about my job?
那我工作的事怎么办
We're gonna have another baby.
我们又要多一个孩子了
Actually, I have an addendum to that.
事实上  我还有要补充的
Please tell me you're about to recite the girl scout oath.
告诉我你这是要背诵女童军守则
No, Tom.
不是的  汤姆
We're having twins...Again.
这一胎又是...双胞胎
I have to go potty.
我想要嘘嘘
Okay, sweetie.
好的  亲爱的
Do you mind pulling over at the next rest stop?
介意开到下一个休息站停一下车吗
We're almost there, buddy. Can you hold it?
就快到了  小子  能憋着吗
No. I really have to go.
不能  憋不住啦
Fine.
好吧
Just hold on a few more minutes.
再憋几分钟就行
Here?
这里吗
He--he can't go here.
这里怎么行呢
Come on, M.J. Let's go.
来  MJ  走吧
Um, can't we find a gas station or maybe a diner?
不能找个加油站或者小饭馆吗
He's a big boy. He can use the bushes.
他不小了  可以再树丛里解决了
- Okay. Here, M.J. Wait for me.
-MJ  等我啊
Don't go too far.
别走太远
Hello?
喂
Dave, detective Collins with the Fairview P.D.
大卫  我是美景镇警局的科林斯侦探
We know everything.
所有事情我们都知道了
I-I'm sorry. What are you--
抱歉  你说什么
Heller, your wife, your child, all of it.
海勒  你妻子  孩子  所有一切
If you come in now, i'll do everything I can to help you.
如果你现在自首  我会尽力帮你
But let's end this before someone gets hurt.
但要在有人受伤前结束这些
Keys.
钥匙
Keys... Oh.
Aah! M.J., run!
MJ  跑啊
Come on, honey! Let's run! Let's run!
来  亲爱的  我们跑
Why are we running?
为什么要跑
We're playing a game with Dave, okay?
我们在和大卫玩游戏  知道吗
So run as fast as you can. Ow! Ow!
所以跑得越快越好
Are you okay?
你没事吧
Aah! Ow! I'm fine.
我没事
Susan! M.J.!
苏珊  MJ
Okay, listen.
听着
It's really important that you win this game.
你一定要设法赢得这游戏
So I want you to find a good hiding place,
你要找个好地方躲起来
And even if you hear Dave,
即使你听到大卫的声音
you don't come out no matter what, okay? Okay?
不管怎样都不要出来  好吗
Don't worry. I'm gonna hide, too. Now go.
别担心  我也会藏起来  快走
Go!
走啊
Where is he?
他在哪
You are not gonna mess this up!
你不能把这搞砸了
We are too close to the finish line!
离成功就差那么一点了
Now call him!
快喊他
Call him.
喊啊
M.J.!
M.J.
Don't come out!
别出来
M.J.!
M.J.
You wanna go fishing, don't you, buddy?
你想去钓鱼  不是吗  小子
if you don't come out now, we're gonna get there too late.
如果你现在不出来  到那里就很晚了
I'll let you drive the boat!
我会让你开船哦
if you don't come out right now, we'll leave without you.
如果你现在不出来  我们就自己走咯
You don't wanna be in this scary graveyard after dark, do you?
你不想天黑后呆在这可怕的墓地  是吗
All right, M.J., We're leaving!
好了  M.J.  我们要走了
Mommy, wake up. I get to drive the boat.
妈咪  醒醒  我可以驾船了
Now keep the volume really high.
把声音开到最大
You don't wanna hear all the boring grown-up talk.
你不会想听无聊的成年人聊天
Buckle up.
系好安全带
What are you gonna do to us?
你会对我们做什么
Shut up. I'm trying to think.
闭嘴  我在想呢
Dave, please...
大卫  求你了
I'm so sorry about that accident.
那次车祸  我很抱歉
You don't wanna hurt M.J. or me.
你不想伤害我和M.J.
You're a good person. I know you.
你是个好人  我了解你
Don't analyze me.
别想分析我
The last guy who tried that didn't do so well.
上回有人这么干  没啥效果
Well, you won't get away with it.
你逃不掉了
Mike already called the cops. They're on their way.
麦克已经报警了  他们在路上了
Enough!
够了
Incoming call, Mike
来电  麦克
Susan? Where are you?
苏珊  你在哪
Not up at the lake.
还没到湖边
- You kind of screwed up my plans here, Mike.
-麦克  你打乱了我的计划
Mike!
麦克
Oh, and, uh, Susan says hello.
刚才苏珊跟你打个招呼
Okay, Dave, take it easy.
大卫  冷静点
You want revenge?
你想报仇吗
Let Susan and M.J. Go. Take me instead.
让苏珊和M.J.走  冲我来
How does it feel, Mike,
麦克  感觉怎样
to know that you can't save the people that you love?
救不了自己所爱的人  是什么感觉
Hopeless?
绝望吗
Like your entire life has no meaning?
像是这一辈子都毫无意义了吗
Dave, please.
大卫  求你了
I-I can't be that far behind you. I'm on route 12.
我离你不远了  我在12号公路上
You're on route 12?
你在12号公路上吗
Yeah. Yeah, come on.
对对  拜托了
You don't wanna hurt them. Let me be the one.
不要伤害他们  冲我来吧
You're right. You should be the one.
你说得对  应该你来
So we've got a deal?
一言为定啊
If I see one cop car, they're both dead.
只要我看到一辆警车  他们俩都得死
No cops. You just tell me where to meet you.
没有警察  告诉我到哪里见你
Keep heading south.
一直往南开
There's an abandoned gas station
在坎特伯雷路
past the intersection of route 12 and canterbury road.
和12号公路交汇处  有个废弃加油站
Canterbury road? That's where we...
坎特伯雷路  那是我们...
Yeah, it is.
就是那
Look familiar?
眼熟吗
What are you gonna do to us?
你要对我们怎样
Why did you bring us here?
干嘛带我们到这来
I thought it would be poetic.
我以为会很诗情画意的
Mike should be here any minute.
麦克随时都会来
Dave, please. Don't hurt mike.
大卫  求你了  别伤害麦克
It wasn't his fault.
不是他的错
No. It was your fault.
对的  是你的错
But he wants to be the hero, so...
但他想做英雄  所以
Get out.
下去
I'm not leaving M.J.
我不会离开M.J.的
M.J.'s coming. I need to set you up first. Get out.
M.J.也会来  我要先搞定你  下去
Now.
快点
Try not to scare M.J. when you bring him here.
带M.J.下来时  不要吓他
Actually, change of plans.
事实上  我改主意了
What?
什么
M.J.'s staying with me.
M.J.和我呆一起
He and I are gonna pull into that intersection
在麦克迅速开过那条路时
just as Mike comes barreling down that road.
M.J.和我将冲出岔口
Oh, my god.
天哪
And you're gonna stay there and watch
而麦克杀死你孩子时
as Mike kills your child,
你就待这看着
just like you killed mine.
就像你杀死我孩子一样
I told you it was poetic.
我告诉过你这很诗意的
Dave, please. Please.
大卫  求你了  拜托了
I cannot imagine the pain you went through,
我无法想像你所经历的痛苦
but you can't do this. You can't kill my little boy!
但你不能这么做  不能杀了我的宝贝
Shut up.
闭嘴
What if your daughter could see you now?!
如果你女儿现在能看见你呢
Is this how you'd want her to see you?!
你想让她看到这样的你吗
As a monster who could murder an innocent child?!
杀害无辜小孩的怪物吗
I'm not a monster.
我不是怪物
Dave! Dave!
大卫  大卫
You don't need that.
你不需要这个
You're a big boy now.
你长大了
Mike!
麦克
Mike! Mike!
麦克  麦克
Stop!
停车
No!
不要啊
M.J.!
M.J.
Mama!
妈妈
Oh, god! are you okay?
天哪  你还好吗
Dave told me to get out of the car.
大卫让我下车的
Mike.
麦克
So what do you say we all go out for ice cream?
我们去吃冰淇淋吧
Oh, i'd love to, but i brought work home.
我很想去  不过我还得工作
Again?
又是工作
I know. i'm so boring.
是啊  无聊至极
Hey, why don't you two go?
要不你俩去吧
Oh, fine. i'll take her now.
好的  我这就带她去
Come on, sweetie.
来吧  亲爱的
Wait.
等等
Don't go.
别走
We have marshmallows and chocolate.
我们有棉花糖和巧克力
I can make s'mores.
我可以做脆香米
Would you like that, my little princess?
你喜欢吗  我的小公主
Yeah!
喜欢
You sure?
你确定吗
You said you had work.
你说你有工作
It can wait.
我可以待会再做
I always have time for my girls.
你们俩才是最重要的
你们母女俩才是最重要的
There was a wedding recently
最近  在美景镇长老会教堂里
At fairview presbyterian church.
有一场盛大的婚礼
The minister spoke about the nature of marriage...
牧师宣读婚姻的本质
The sublime joy of giving birth...
给予新生命的至乐
The immense pleasure of raising a family...
呵护家庭所得的无与伦比的快乐
The importance of life long fidelity...
对婚姻忠诚的重要性
And then he said what all ministers say
最后他像所有牧师一样
To conclude such matters...
做了最后的结语
You may now kiss the bride.
可以吻新娘了
For a moment,
在这时
The groom wondered if he was doing the right thing.
新郎还在犹豫他做的抉择  是否正确
That's when the bells began to ring,
这时教堂钟声响起
告诉他  是对的
Telling him he had.